Now,
let's welcome our mystery guest!
Hello everyone.
I'm the CEO of Gufeng Group,
Cheng An.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
President An is here today and has brought us
a lot of perks.
Isn't that right?
That's right.
Cheng An,
you actually stepped in for that bitch.
Tonight,
we have prepared for everyone
many, many perks.
Otherwise,
just let President An finish the stream.
The first 100 viewers to place an order tonight...
No.
Wan Niang is our partner streamer.
If she doesn't show up,
the fans will doubt our partnership.
Here's the plan.
You keep an eye on things.
I'll go find her.
That's right.
It's very smooth on the palate.
For this wine,
it's best to decant it for 30 minutes.
That's the best time to taste it.
Such professional knowledge on decanting.
Those of you who drink often
can learn a bit about it.
That's right.
Wan Niang.
Open the door.
The door's unlocked.
Come in.
The livestream has already started.
You're late.
Isn't this our high-and-mighty Director Sang?
What?
You came to invite me personally?
However,
I, Wan Niang, am not someone just anyone can order around.
We have an agreement for the livestream.
If you don't go,
Gufeng Group will sue you.
Even if I lose the case,
how much would I have to pay?
But if the new product livestream is ruined,
all of Gufeng Group's investments
will go down the drain.
When that happens, Director Sang,
how will you explain it to the Board of Directors?
Name your terms.
What will it take for you to stream?
Very simple.
Get Lin Wanmei to come invite me.
Instead of monitoring the stream at the office,
why did you come home to slack off?
About Wan Niang,
I know you're the one pulling the strings.
But for Gufeng Group, this livestream
is absolutely crucial.
We can't let our personal grudge
ruin everyone's hard work.
What a pity.
I'm no longer the VP of Gufeng Group.
What does Gufeng Group's business
have to do with me?
Don't you just want to return to Gufeng Group?
I like talking to smart people.
It's a deal.
Lin Wanmei,
what exactly are you doing?
Your feud with Sang Luo
has severely affected the company.
So you're here to call me to account.
The live stream for the new product launch was almost ruined.
Sang Luo was in charge of the live stream.
So,
I can't help it if she messed it up.
Listen to me carefully.
I won't get involved in your personal grudges.
But
if you dare to affect the company,
I won't let you get away with it.
Aren't you getting involved right now?
I just want to take back
what belongs to me.
Cheng An, you don't have to help me,
but please don't help Sang Luo
block my path.
Otherwise,
things will get ugly for everyone.
I'm warning you,
don't play with fire.
It's getting late.
Still working?
I thought after that livestream incident,
you'd be really upset.
What's the point of being upset?
I was careless this time.
I should reflect on it.
I'm really glad
you see it that way.
Here.
I have something for you.
I hope it brings you good luck.
Why do you like folding paper cranes so much?
Because paper cranes
can bring us good luck.
Little Uncle is so cheap.
Trying to brush me off with just a paper crane.
This crane...
if it's really as magical as you say
and can bring good luck...
Then what was all my suffering for?
You can't possibly not know.
Give this piece of junk to a kid,
and even they wouldn't want it.
But about the livestream,
thanks for helping me out.
That's a separate matter.
You're back so late.
Where were you running wild?
The new product's livestream sales hit a record high.
We in the R&D department
went out for a team dinner.
The R&D department
is managed by Luo Luo.
What does that have to do with you?
You're a daughter-in-law of the Cheng family.
Staying out all night like this...
This is improper!
Luo Luo is here!
Come, come, come.
It's so late.
You must be exhausted.
I'm fine.
Some people, however,
achieve a tiny bit of success,
and immediately
get carried away.
Not like you,
so down-to-earth.
Always putting the company first.
Sang Luo.
I specially stewed this
bird's nest soup for you.
This is for
Sang Luo.
Tastes good.
Giving such nourishing stuff to a useless person,
isn't it a waste?
Right, Sang Luo?
Lin Wanmei!
You've only achieved a tiny bit of success,
now you throw your weight around in the Cheng family?
It's not your place to speak in this house.
What are you saying, Mom?
Even with your backing,
if Sang Luo's abilities are lacking,
she won't be able to win people over.
Consider this incident a lesson.
Sang Luo,
remember in the future to
guard against arrogance and impatience.
It's delicious.
I...
I'm fine.
If it weren't for Feng's child,
I wouldn't tolerate her for another day.
Don't panic, Auntie.
Just getting you a new tool for pruning flowers.
Sang Luo,
since you've already lost,
stop playing these petty tricks.
Auntie Lin,
you may enjoy this brief victory,
but be careful, extreme joy begets sorrow.
Zhao Yue,
the garbage you brewed
is completely useless to the company.
Keep it for yourself.
Before you hit a dog, look at its master.
Your master is a loser
who can't protect you at all.
Then can your master
protect a mad dog like you?
You've been a dog so long, you see everyone as one.
Director Sang.
Feeling sorry for your little sidekick?
She's just a pushover.
I can push her around
however I want.
You...
right this instant,
apologize to Zhao Yue.
I won't apologize.
What are you going to do about it?
Listen to me carefully, Xiaoxiao.
Today is the last time.
If it happens again,
just see what happens.
I must be seeing things.
Zhao Yue.
Over here! Over here!
This is Chu Yan's photo.
How did it get here?
Looking,
looking,
That's the voice!
Find a Friend,
found a
Stop singing!
good friend.
What's going on?
Salute,
Go after the one
responsible.
and shake hands.
I didn't kill you!
You are my
Stay away from me!
Looking,
looking,
Find a Friend,
You are my
What are you doing?
Let me go!
You!
What the hell do you want?
Do you know
how absurd your actions were tonight?
Let go, you're hurting me!
I'm not letting go until you explain yourself.
What you did at the R&D center tonight
showed zero regard for the consequences.
If anything happened to Xiaoxiao,
how would the company explain it?
She deserved it.
I have my own plans.
It's none of your business.
Plans?
You're completely out of line.
The company isn't a place for your personal vendettas.
No matter what,
you shouldn't resort to such childish tactics.
First,
Xiaoxiao brought it on herself.
Second,
I know what I'm doing.
Third,
it won't hurt President An's company.
Happy now?
Get away from me.
Hello?
President An,
something's happened at the company.
You good-for-nothing!
What the hell are you all doing?!
Delete all the rumors right now!
Look into it!
Find out who it is.
I'll destroy them!
What's going on?
President An, you're finally here.
It's all over the internet now.
Negative posts about the company's power-for-sex scandal
driving a female employee to suicide.
They spread all over the internet overnight.
It's already in the top three on Trending.
This definitely isn't a normal online leak.
The timing is too perfect,
and the content is highly targeted.
Split into two groups.
The IT department,
contact a reliable cybersecurity firm
to help us trace the source of the posts.
Got it.
The PR department,
prepare a statement,
but don't release it yet.
Wait until we figure this out.
Understood.
And President Yan...
President Yan,
contact our friends in the media.
See if they can
push some positive press releases
to ease the public pressure.
Xiao Yang,
contact the media.
Contact the media!
Get us off Trending!
What if...
we can't divert the topic?
If we can't divert it,
we'll face the problem head-on.
Everyone,
prepare Crisis PR countermeasures,
including
releasing a statement,
a media Q&A,
and follow-up actions.
The company can't withstand
this kind of loss of trust.
Do you understand?
Understood.
Understood, understood.
Do as President An says.
Okay, okay. Don't be afraid.
Take your time.
Give it a try.
That's right.
You go that way.
Let's try taking a walk.
Auntie Lin,
Xiao Shen,
You seem a bit distracted today.
Do I?
Maybe it's because the water is a bit cold today.
I'm not feeling too well.
Why isn't President Lin getting in the water with us?
Coach Shen.
President Lin is pregnant.
Pregnant?
I really couldn't tell.
You've kept your figure so well.
I'm a little tired.
Go rest for a while if you're tired.
President Lin.
You need to take care of your health.
Don't catch a cold.
Drink some hot water.
Be mindful of the baby.
Mind your own business.
Mom.
There's an emergency at the company.
I need to go handle it.
I can't stay with you today.
They say men who work hard are the most charming.
But honestly, I think women who focus on their careers...
...have a certain charm too.
Was I talking to you?
Let's go.
L-let's practice some more.
Don't be mad.
Xiaoxiao,
I have some bad news for you.
You need to brace yourself.
Master.
I know I haven't been at my best lately.
I'll get back on track.
Don't worry.
You're fired.
It's a decision from upper management.
The recent online scandal had a huge impact.
And as for you...
...a lot of colleagues complained about you.
So there's no other choice.
I fought for you.
But I couldn't sway their decision.
You've been with me for so many years.
I won't treat you unfairly.
Even outside the company...
...you and I...
...will always be Master and apprentice.
I've worked my fingers to the bone for you for years!
I've done so much of your dirty work!
Even if I don't get any credit...
...my hard work should count for something, right?
And now...
...you're trying to fool me with this crap?
You want to just kick me to the curb?
Not a chance!
As for what happened to Chu Yan...
...you were the mastermind behind it.
I was just a minor player...
...who added fuel to the fire.
If I tell everyone the truth...
...do you think your fate...
...will be any better than mine?
The wine influencer who visited Gufeng Group the other day
highly praised our warm hospitality
and specifically complimented Chu Yan,
saying she has great potential.
His feature article has been published online,
and the feedback from netizens is extremely enthusiastic.
You did a great job.
From now on,
find more talents like Chu Yan.
Understood?
President Lin.
I saw how much that influencer valued her.
I just wanted to get a piece of the pie.
I'm sorry, President Lin.
I'm sorry.
So quick to spill your guts, huh?
President Lin.
Everything went smoothly.
Good.
Keep an eye on her.
Let her do what she's supposed to do.
Then
what do you want?
Cut the crap.
Five million.
And I'll step out of Gufeng Group.
I won't say another word about your dirty deeds.
In here
is all the evidence of you bullying Chu Yan and Zhao Yue.
Guess
if the truth of Chu Yan's death is exposed,
who will be seen as the real murderer?
Tear it up.
Tear it all you want.
I definitely have backups of this.
There's money in here.
I advise you to take it
and pack your things and leave immediately.
Don't make things end up
looking ugly for everyone.
Just you wait.
This whole thing
won't be settled so easily.
Dongdong,
with the surveillance and hacker stuff,
thanks so much for your help.
Dongdong really knows his stuff.
He's faster than my own guys.
He's more talented than we thought.
Sang Luo.
Let me see.
All done.
Take a look.
It's fixed.
When did you learn all this?
I'm at home every day.
With computers,
you just learn by playing around.
If you ever have any computer issues,
Sang Luo,
you can always come to me.
What else can you do besides this?
Network technology.
Anyway, anything related to basic computing,
I know a little bit about.
Does that mean you're like a...
hacker?
Hack...
Sang Luo,
I haven't done anything bad!
I...
Sang Luo,
about this...
could you not tell Grandma?
She doesn't like me messing with this stuff.
She always thinks
I'm not doing anything serious.
Okay.
Letting him help you
is the greatest validation for him.
Being able to help you, Sang Luo,
makes me really happy.
Now that Xiaoxiao has fallen out with Lin Wanmei,
all we need is someone
to give them a little push.
You altered my decision without authorization,
stopping the employees from working overtime.
Are you trying to provoke me?
The R&D department is tired enough already.
I just don't want more people going crazy, okay?
Gufeng Group is not a charity.
I pay them such high salaries,
so they must create the value I demand.
President Lin.
Is the value you demand driving employees crazy
and having them bring down Gufeng Group with a lawsuit?
Do you have any idea
that Zhao Yue's parents already sued you at the Department of Labor?
It's because of your negligence as a manager
that Xiaoxiao was able to bully Zhao Yue at work.
This was already a liability for Gufeng Group.
If I hadn't compensated Zhao Yue's parents,
do you think you'd still be standing here talking to me?
These documents
would already be on a desk at the Department of Labor.
Could you bear the consequences?
Fine.
You win.
Psycho.
Unbelievable.
Kill two birds with one stone.
You used the ghost incident
to abolish Lin Wanmei's overtime rule.
You dealt a blow to her authority,
drove a wedge between her and Xiaoxiao,
and won over the R&D department.
Isn't that killing two birds with one stone?
What are you gonna do about it?
I don't want to do anything to you.
But I know
that your true goal
is not just about Chu Yan, is it?